http://www.mvremix.com/urban/privacy.php3

| STORE | VIDEOS | INTERVIEWS | REVIEWS | BLOGS | ARTICLES | COLUMNS | MESSAGE BOARD | LINKS | BOOKMARK |
MVRemix has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: MVRemix.com
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address for other purposes, to be aware of where our visitors are stemming from around the globe.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Personal Information
This website does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. MVRemix Media is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Contacting the Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: privacy@mvremix.com
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
- MVRemix Staff
|
About Us | Site Map | Privacy Policy | Contact Us |
© 2014 MVRemix Media
